<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Control on ForzaETH</title>
    <link>https://forzaeth.ch/categories/control/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Control on ForzaETH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://forzaeth.ch/categories/control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MAP Paper</title>
      <link>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/map_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/map_paper/</guid>
      <description>MAP Paper A big reason for the teams outstanding performance at the F1TENTH Grand Prix is our Path tracking controller. Developed by thesis students for our first Race at ICRA 2022, the Model- and Acceleration-based Pursuit controller allows us to track our racing line at speeds close to the limit of friction. The paper was published and presented at the International Conference on Robotics and Automation 2023 in London.&#xA;Abstract Autonomous racing is a research field gaining large popularity, as it pushes autonomous driving algorithms to their limits and serves as a catalyst for general autonomous driving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TC-Driver: A Trajectory Conditioned Reinforcement Learning Approach to Zero-Shot Autonomous Racing</title>
      <link>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/tc_driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/tc_driver/</guid>
      <description>TC-Driver Abstract Autonomous racing is becoming popular for academic and industry researchers as a test for general autonomous driving by pushing perception, planning, and control algorithms to their limits. While traditional control methods such as model predictive control are capable of generating an optimal control sequence at the edge of the vehicles’ physical controllability, these methods are sensitive to the accuracy of the modeling parameters, such as tire modeling coefficients. As model mismatch is inevitable in reality, the heuristic nature of Reinforcement Learning (RL) offers a viable approach to modeling robustness.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
