<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Control on ForzaETH</title>
    <link>https://forzaeth.ch/categories/control/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Control on ForzaETH</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://forzaeth.ch/categories/control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Model- and Acceleration-based Pursuit (MAP) Controller for High-Performance Autonomous Racing</title>
      <link>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/map_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/map_paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;map-paper&#34;&gt;MAP Paper&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A big reason for the teams outstanding performance at the F1TENTH Grand Prix is our Path tracking controller. Developed by thesis students for our first Race at ICRA 2022, the Model- and Acceleration-based Pursuit controller allows us to track our racing line at speeds close to the limit of friction. The paper was published and presented at the International Conference on Robotics and Automation 2023 in London.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Autonomous racing is a research field gaining large popularity, as it pushes autonomous driving algorithms to their limits and serves as a catalyst for general autonomous driving. For scaled autonomous racing platforms, the computational constraint and complexity often limit the use of Model Predictive Control (MPC). As a consequence, geometric controllers are the most frequently deployed controllers. They prove to be performant while yielding implementation and operational simplicity. Yet, they inherently lack the incorporation of model dynamics, thus limiting the race car to a velocity domain where tire slip can be neglected. This paper presents Model- and Acceleration-based Pursuit (MAP) a high-performance model-based trajectory tracking algorithm that preserves the simplicity of geometric approaches while leveraging tire dynamics. The proposed algorithm allows accurate tracking of a trajectory at unprecedented velocities compared to State-of-the-Art (SotA) geometric controllers. The MAP controller is experimentally validated and outperforms the reference geometric controller four-fold in terms of lateral tracking error, yielding a tracking error of 0.055m at tested speeds up to 11m/s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TC-Driver: A Trajectory Conditioned Reinforcement Learning Approach to Zero-Shot Autonomous Racing</title>
      <link>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/tc_driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forzaeth.ch/blog/tc_driver/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tc-driver&#34;&gt;TC-Driver&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Autonomous racing is becoming popular for academic and industry researchers as a test&#xA;for general autonomous driving by pushing perception, planning, and control algorithms to their&#xA;limits. While traditional control methods such as model predictive control are capable of generating&#xA;an optimal control sequence at the edge of the vehicles’ physical controllability, these methods are&#xA;sensitive to the accuracy of the modeling parameters, such as tire modeling coefficients. As model&#xA;mismatch is inevitable in reality, the heuristic nature of Reinforcement Learning (RL) offers a viable&#xA;approach to modeling robustness. This paper presents TC-Driver, an RL approach for robust control&#xA;in autonomous racing. In particular, the TC-Driver agent is conditioned by a trajectory generated&#xA;by any arbitrary traditional high-level trajectory planner. The proposed TC-Driver architecture&#xA;addresses the tire parameter modeling inaccuracies by exploiting the learning capabilities of RL while&#xA;utilizing the reliability of traditional planning methods in a hybrid fashion. We train the agent under&#xA;varying tire conditions, allowing it to generalize to different model parameters, aiming to increase&#xA;the racing capabilities of the system in practice. Experimental results demonstrate that the proposed&#xA;hybrid RL architecture of the TC-Driver improves the generalization robustness of autonomous&#xA;racing agents when compared to a previous state-of-the-art end-to-end-based architecture. Namely,&#xA;the proposed controller yields a 29-fold improvement in crash ratio when facing model mismatch&#xA;and can zero-shot transfer its behavior on unseen tracks which present completely new features,&#xA;while the end-to-end baseline fails. When deployed on a physical system, the proposed architecture&#xA;demonstrates zero-shot Sim2Real capabilities that outperform end-to-end agents 10-fold in terms&#xA;of crash ratio while exhibiting similar driving characteristics in reality as in simulation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
