<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Race on ForzaETH</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/race/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Race on ForzaETH</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/race/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IV 2025 Roboracer Competition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/iv_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/iv_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week, our team had the opportunity to compete in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://roboracer.ai/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;25th Roboracer Competition&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, held during the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieee-iv.org/2025/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intelligent Vehicles Symposium 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the beautiful city of &lt;em&gt;Cluj-Napoca, Romania&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The track, while visually simple, turned out to be deceptively difficult. A thick layer of dust on the floor created low-friction conditions that made precise control difficult and impacted system identification.&#xA;The race was not just about raw speed, adaptibility and consistency turned out to be the deciding factors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICRA 2025 Roboracer Competition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, ForzaETH secured 3rd place at the Roboracer Competition at ICRA25 in Atlanta USA!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The racetrack was long and narrow, combining high-speed straights with technical sections featuring tight corners and slalom sequences. The medium-grip surface with discontinuities made it even more challenging. The team had to work hard to find the right balance between speed and reliability, pushing the car to its limits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After qualifying in P6 with a tough time trial session, we fought our way up the race bracket, facing five teams. We competed in the semifinal of the double elimination bracket and the final of the losers bracket.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC 2024 roboracer GP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/cdc_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/cdc_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We wrapped up 2024 with an exciting race at the The Roboracer Foundation 22nd roboracer Autonomous Grand Prix at CDC24 in Milano.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our primary objective was to test our reinforcement learning (RL) controller, which presented unique challenges. The track&amp;rsquo;s rapidly changing grip conditions, caused by dust accumulation, complicated our policy training. Adapting to the intricate tire-floor dynamics proved difficult, making it challenging to outperform our existing MAP controller.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The competition wasn&amp;rsquo;t without its dramatic moments. A collision with another car resulted in significant hardware damage, breaking the servo and damaging the driveshaft. However, our team&amp;rsquo;s resilience shined through as we performed an intensive overnight repair, bringing the car back to racing condition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IROS 2024 roboracer GP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/iros_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/iros_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ForzaETH race team once again raced at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://iros2024-race.f1tenth.org/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;21st roboracer Autonomous Grand Prix&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://iros2024-abudhabi.org/&#34;&gt;IROS 2024&lt;/a&gt; in Abu Dhabi, UAE. Following our 3rd place finish in Japan, the team worked hard to try to reclaim the title.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The floor surface at IROS proved to be extremely grippy carpet. While the track area was smaller than at previous competitions, the track layout was technical, with sweeping corners, a hairpin, and chicanes. By our estimates, this would provide more than twice the lateral grip than we faced in Japan. This was a surprise to us, as we had spent most of the preparation time on lower-grip surfaces. Would our hardware and software be up for the task in this unfamiliar grip regime?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICRA 2024 roboracer GP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ForzaETH race team participated in the &lt;em&gt;15th roboracer Autonomous Racing Competition&lt;/em&gt; at the International Conference on Robotics and Automation in Yokohama, Japan. Our team, consisting of five students with diverse expertise in robotics, spent several months preparing our cars and rehearsing racing procedures. For the first time, the race team was entirely student-led and consisted of bachelor and master students.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon arriving in Japan, we immediately began training to optimize the tuning process. However, issues with the internet connection made the process considerably harder as live telemetry from the car was unavailable. Despite this setback, our familiarity with the car allowed us to achieve impressive lap times. During the time-trials phase, we qualified in 3rd place out of 18 teams from around the world, positioning us well for the head-to-head phase of the tournament.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indy Autonomous Challenge SIM Race</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/iac_sim_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/iac_sim_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A team comprised of five master students secured a prestigious second place in the Indy autonomous race simulation at the tech event CES in Las Vegas. This marked a first step in extending the ForzaETH Race Stack to full-scale autonomous racing.&#xA;ForzaETH’s team was only surpassed by the experienced PoliMOVE Autonomous Racing Team from Politecnico di Milano. An exceptional and very promising achievement for the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ee.ethz.ch/de/news-und-veranstaltungen/d-itet-news-channel/2024/01/silver-medal-for-pbls-autonomous-racing-team-forzaeth-at-ces-in-las-vegas.html&#34;&gt;Article on the ETH D-ITET Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICRA 2023 roboracer GP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A dedicated team of six students devoted their efforts to enhancing the autonomous racing stack through their bachelor, semester, and master theses. Their research led to significant improvements in the localization, obstacle detection, and control aspects of our autonomous racing cars.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Following a semester filled with rigorous work and preparation, we eagerly entered the roboracer Grand Prix at the International Conference on Robotics and Automation, where 22 teams from around the world vied for the prestigious title.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Race</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/germany_22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/germany_22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On August 20 and 21, 2022, the ForzaETH team participated in its second race at the roboracer Grand Prix held at the Lausitzring Eurospeedway racetrack. Nine teams were in contention for victory during this tournament.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the initial day of the competition, the team demonstrated exceptional performance by securing the top position in the qualifying phase. They achieved this feat by completing the most consecutive laps in five minutes and recording the fastest lap time. This outstanding performance granted them the coveted pole position for the head-to-head competition scheduled for the second day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICRA 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/icra_22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A group of students, consisting of three undergraduates and one master&amp;rsquo;s student, formed the inaugural Race Team. Together, they dedicated themselves to creating advanced path planning algorithms, obstacle detection systems, and velocity and path tracking controllers. Following a semester of relentless effort, the team entered its first competition — the roboracer Grand Prix held at the International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA) in Philadelphia. The event attracted 20 teams from around the globe, all fighting for the win. Against stiff competition, the ForzaETH team delivered an outstanding performance, securing an impressive 4th place finish and with that performing the best out of all the newbie teams. This success motivates further develop our racing algorithms and go for the win at the next roboracer Race.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
